Contact

320 W Republican, Suite 207 Seattle, Washington 98119 206-478-5028 (Mobile) inquiries@aquoco.co

www.linkedin.com/in/aquocotrans (LinkedIn) aaert.org (Other) aquoco.co (Personal)

Top Skills

Depositions
Litigation
Editing

Certifications

Certified Agency Typist

Notary Public

Certified Electronic Reporter & Transcriber, Corporate Member Microsoft Office Master 2016

Publications

Dueling for Profit

Dueling for Profit

Gaming in Your World: South Korea Part 1 & 2

There's More to Gaming than Just Gaming

These Kids Built an Eco Village

Erica Ingram

Owner of A Quo Co.

Greater Seattle Area

Summary

Experienced certified transcriber with a demonstrated history in the legal services industry.

Related programming experience in Access databases and VBA. Some demonstration of programming skills at https://www.hackerrank.com/evoingram and https://github.com/evoingram/. Searching for a part-time remote developer position using Python and/or VBA.

Experience

A Quo Co. Owner May 2009 - Present United States

General & legal transcription services of digital audio and video formats. All transcripts include hyperlinking of authority mentioned during court proceedings to Google Scholar, .gov sites, and the like as well as tables of authority on the cert page and free working copies of your transcript so you can use the normal features of Word within the transcript to highlight, bold, and the like as you see fit. Word indexes and condensed versions are also included for free. You will not get more value from another court transcription service; nobody provides the same level of legal research and saves you as much time as we do with our transcripts.

Freelance Author Freelance Author July 2000 - Present

Book - Secrets of a Teenager, other magazine articles including but not limited to ET-Center, Gamer's Quarter, Spirituality & Health, Team Pandemic News, Massive Magazine, and Computer Games Magazine.

American Association of Electronic Reporters and Transcribers, Inc. Proctor

March 2012 - January 2014 (1 year 11 months)

Seattle

Proctor AAERT certification examinations.

Continental Reporting Service

Transcriber

May 2009 - October 2011 (2 years 6 months)

- -transcribing hearings, depositions, examinations under oath, trials, and various court proceedings from digital audio
- -preparing transcripts for official production

Continental Reporting Service

Data Entry/Calendar Department

March 2005 - October 2010 (5 years 8 months)

- -heavy business to business and legal correspondence
- -heavy telephone usage
- -utilize various business application software.
- -responsible for communicating, anticipating and meeting client needs
- -scheduling depositions and deposition services
- -following exact scheduling & confirmation process to eliminate all mistakes
- -regularly meet very tight deadlines and work under extreme pressure sometimes.

eSports TV

Editor in Chief

August 2006 - September 2007 (1 year 2 months)

- -Keeping info, video, and highlights up to date for three shows.
- -ten news articles per week.
- -oversee News Department and coordinate News Department with other Departments.
- -assist Marketing Department as needed.
- -Write promotional blurbs for three shows.
- grammar, editing of all press releases and some writing.
- -upkeep deadlines for staff writers

TeamWarfare League

General News Department Manager

May 2006 - September 2007 (1 year 5 months)

- -TeamWarfare has a readership of 500,000 people.
- -Wrote two feature articles per month for web, including HTML.

- -Wrote one monthly column for web, including HTML.
- -Wrote one to two press releases per week for web, including HTML.
- -Oversees three to six staff writers.
- -Ensures production and workflow are running smoothly and on time.
- -Ensures staff concerns are taken care of appropriately.
- -Ensures procedure, rules, copyright laws, and sponsorship regulations are being followed.
- -Assists staff writers with HTML and page layout/design when necessary.

FedexKinkos

Senior Project Manager

October 2002 - February 2005 (2 years 5 months)

- -oversee and supervise production workflow, deadlines, and quality standards.
- -utilize various business application software.
- -cash management and daily sales reports.
- -photocopy, print, bind, assemble, and collate documents and projects as needed.
- -team member motivation.
- -maintain clean, easily accessible and well-organized production zone.
- -create documents and graphics as needed on appropriate software programs.
- -responsible for communicating and anticipating customer needs.

Education

Danville Junior-Senior High School

High School Diploma, College Preparatory · (1995 - 1999)